Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: World War II (radio commentators tour of the war fronts), 1945; 1 (Box 1564)
    - Verso: 43. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany 10 Apr. 1945. German civilians in line waiting outside "Town Major's Hqts" on "Kaiser-Wilhelm-Ring" strasse, in Cologne, Germany, 1-verso
    - 44. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany 10 Apr. 1945. Cologne, Germany in ruins after bombers of the 9th Air Force bombed the city, 2
    - Verso: 44. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany 10 Apr. 1945. Cologne, Germany in ruins after bombers of the 9th Air Force bombed the city, 2-verso
    - 44. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany 10 Apr. 1945. Cologne, Germany in ruins after bombers of the 9th Air Force bombed the city, 3
    - Verso: 44. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany 10 Apr. 1945. Cologne, Germany in ruins after bombers of the 9th Air Force bombed the city, 3-verso
    - 45. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany 10 Apr. 1945. Members of the Radio Correspondents party walking in the ruined streets of Cologne, Germany, 4
    - Verso: 45. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany 10 Apr. 1945. Members of the Radio Correspondents party walking in the ruined streets of Cologne, Germany, 4-verso
    - 46. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany. 10 Apr. 1945 Quincy Howe, C.B.S. holds "Hitler" stamps which are being shown to him by Pfc. Charles P. Watts, of Port Royal, Va., 5
    - Verso: 46. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany. 10 Apr. 1945 Quincy Howe, C.B.S. holds "Hitler" stamps which are being shown to him by Pfc. Charles P. Watts, of Port Royal, Va., 5-verso
    - 47. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Eschwege, Germany 14 Apr. 1945 Capt. Robert F. Thomas, Merced City, Calif., C.O. of the 107th Tactical Squadron shown alongside his plane with one of the remote control cameras he uses, 6
    - Verso: 47. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Eschwege, Germany 14 Apr. 1945 Capt. Robert F. Thomas, Merced City, Calif., C.O. of the 107th Tactical Squadron shown alongside his plane with one of the remote control cameras he uses, 6-verso
    - 48. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Eschwege, Germany 14 Apr. 1945. Sgt. Thomas B. Bowen, Memphis, Tenn. explaining the "Snooper" to Howard Barnes, George Hamilton Combs, and Johannes Steel, 7
    - Verso: 48. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Eschwege, Germany 14 Apr. 1945. Sgt. Thomas B. Bowen, Memphis, Tenn. explaining the "Snooper" to Howard Barnes, George Hamilton Combs, and Johannes Steel, 7-verso
    - 49. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Eschwege, Germany 14 Apr. 1945. 1st Lt. Luther B. Smith of Louisville, Kentucky who has flown 78 missions over Normandy, Northern France and Germany is shown in front of some pictures taken by his Squadron, 8
    - Verso: 49. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Eschwege, Germany 14 Apr. 1945. 1st Lt. Luther B. Smith of Louisville, Kentucky who has flown 78 missions over Normandy, Northern France and Germany is shown in front of some pictures taken by his Squadron, 8-verso
    - 51. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany 10 Apr. 1945. L. to R.; Quincy Howe, C.B.S. Cesar Saerchinger, N.B.C. and John W. Vandercook, N.B.C. leaving the Cathedral after inspecting the interior, 9
    - Verso: 51. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany 10 Apr. 1945. L. to R.; Quincy Howe, C.B.S. Cesar Saerchinger, N.B.C. and John W. Vandercook, N.B.C. leaving the Cathedral after inspecting the interior, 9-verso
    - 53. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany. 10 Apr. 1945. Cesar Saerchinger, N.B.C. and Quincy Howe, C.B.S. looking over knocked out German tank in front of Cathedral, 10
    - Verso: 53. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany. 10 Apr. 1945. Cesar Saerchinger, N.B.C. and Quincy Howe, C.B.S. looking over knocked out German tank in front of Cathedral, 10-verso
    - 59. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Mainz, Germany Rhine River. 19 Apr. 1945. Pontoon bridge spanning the Rhine River at Mainz, Germany, 11
    - Verso: 59. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Mainz, Germany Rhine River. 19 Apr. 1945. Pontoon bridge spanning the Rhine River at Mainz, Germany, 11-verso
    - 60. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Gutersloh Airfield, Germany 12 Apr. 1945. The "Manfred FRHR. Von Richtohofen Haus," This is the entrance to the administration building of the 67th Tactical Recon. Group formerly used by the Nazis, 12
    - Verso: 60. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Gutersloh Airfield, Germany 12 Apr. 1945. The "Manfred FRHR. Von Richtohofen Haus," This is the entrance to the administration building of the 67th Tactical Recon. Group formerly used by the Nazis, 12-verso
    - 61. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Gutersloh Airfield, Germany 12 Apr. 1945. Radio Commentators over the wrecked hangars of the Gutersloh Airfield, Germany, 13
    - Verso: 61. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Gutersloh Airfield, Germany 12 Apr. 1945. Radio Commentators over the wrecked hangars of the Gutersloh Airfield, Germany, 13-verso
    - 62. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Gutersloh Airfield, Germany 12 Apr. 1945. Howard Barnes, W.O.R. looking at wreath placed by Germans on losing Gutersloh Airfield to the Americans, 14
    - Verso: 62. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Gutersloh Airfield, Germany 12 Apr. 1945. Howard Barnes, W.O.R. looking at wreath placed by Germans on losing Gutersloh Airfield to the Americans, 14-verso
    - 63. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Gutersloh, Germany. 12 Apr. 1945. Old World War I painting of Manfred Von Richtohofen's plane. Looking on are Lt. William E. Dougherty, Pilot of our C-47, and Joseph Harsch, C.B.S., 15
    - Verso: 63. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Gutersloh, Germany. 12 Apr. 1945. Old World War I painting of Manfred Von Richtohofen's plane. Looking on are Lt. William E. Dougherty, Pilot of our C-47, and Joseph Harsch, C.B.S., 15-verso
    - 64. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Ober-Olm, Germany 17 Apr. 1945. Lt. Col. Glenn Eagleston, of Alhambra, Calif. Left, and Lowell Thomas, talking on the field at Ober-Olm, Germany, base for the 354th Fighter Group, 16
    - Verso: 64. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Ober-Olm, Germany 17 Apr. 1945. Lt. Col. Glenn Eagleston, of Alhambra, Calif. Left, and Lowell Thomas, talking on the field at Ober-Olm, Germany, base for the 354th Fighter Group, 16-verso
    - 65. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Ober-Olm, Germany 17 Apr. 1945. L. to R.: Sgt. Earl Osborn, Lowell Thomas, N.B.C. Lt. B.W. Carr, and Lt. Col. Jack Bradley, Deputy C.O. of 354th Fighter Group, 17
    - Verso: 65. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Ober-Olm, Germany 17 Apr. 1945. L. to R.: Sgt. Earl Osborn, Lowell Thomas, N.B.C. Lt. B.W. Carr, and Lt. Col. Jack Bradley, Deputy C.O. of 354th Fighter Group, 17-verso
    - 65. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Ober-Olm, Germany 17 Apr. 1945. L. to R.: Sgt. Earl Osborn, Lowell Thomas, N.B.C. Lt. B.W. Carr, and Lt. Col. Jack Bradley, Deputy C.O. of 354th Fighter Group, 18
    - 66. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Mainz, Germany. Apr. 1945. An ambulance about to cross the Pontoon bridge spanning the Rhine River at Mainz, Germany, 19
    - Verso: 66. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Mainz, Germany. Apr. 1945. An ambulance about to cross the Pontoon bridge spanning the Rhine River at Mainz, Germany, 19-verso
    - 67. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Near Eschwege, Germany 18 Apr. 1945. A wrecked German gun in field near Eschwege, Germany with a farmer and his horse working in the field, 20
    - Verso: 67. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Near Eschwege, Germany 18 Apr. 1945. A wrecked German gun in field near Eschwege, Germany with a farmer and his horse working in the field, 20-verso
    - 67. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Near Eschwege, Germany 18 Apr. 1945. A wrecked German gun in field near Eschwege, Germany with a farmer and his horse working in the field, 21
    - Verso: 67. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Near Eschwege, Germany 18 Apr. 1945. A wrecked German gun in field near Eschwege, Germany with a farmer and his horse working in the field, 21-verso
    - 68. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Mainz, Germany. Apr. 1945. Pontoon Bridge spanning the Rhine River at Mainz, Germany, 22
    - Verso: 68. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Mainz, Germany. Apr. 1945. Pontoon Bridge spanning the Rhine River at Mainz, Germany, 22-verso
    - 68. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Mainz, Germany. Apr. 1945. Pontoon Bridge spanning the Rhine River at Mainz, Germany, 23
    - Verso: 68. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Mainz, Germany. Apr. 1945. Pontoon Bridge spanning the Rhine River at Mainz, Germany, 23-verso
    - 70. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Wiesbaden, Germany 15 Apr. 1945. A mother and her child only two of the thousands of displaced persons cared for by U.S. Army Forces in the camp in Wiesbaden, Germany, 24
    - Verso: 70. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Wiesbaden, Germany 15 Apr. 1945. A mother and her child only two of the thousands of displaced persons cared for by U.S. Army Forces in the camp in Wiesbaden, Germany, 24-verso
    - 70. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Wiesbaden, Germany 15 Apr. 1945. A mother and her child only two of the thousands of displaced persons cared for by U.S. Army Forces in the camp in Wiesbaden, Germany, 25
    - Verso: 70. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Wiesbaden, Germany 15 Apr. 1945. A mother and her child only two of the thousands of displaced persons cared for by U.S. Army Forces in the camp in Wiesbaden, Germany, 25-verso
    - 71. Radio Commentators Tour war Fronts. Wiesbaden, Germany. 15 Apr. 1945. Lt. Col. Leroy Gowart, MGO. Of Wiesbaden, Germany talking to group of Radio Commentators in his office at "Town Major's" Headquarters, 26
    - Verso: 71. Radio Commentators Tour war Fronts. Wiesbaden, Germany. 15 Apr. 1945. Lt. Col. Leroy Gowart, MGO. Of Wiesbaden, Germany talking to group of Radio Commentators in his office at "Town Major's" Headquarters, 26-verso
    - 72. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Juvencourt Airfield, France. 11 Apr. 1945. Col. Robert Hughey, C.O. of Juvencourt Airfield left, talking to Lowell Thomas, N.B.C. in cock-pit of an A-26, 27
    - Verso: 72. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Juvencourt Airfield, France. 11 Apr. 1945. Col. Robert Hughey, C.O. of Juvencourt Airfield left, talking to Lowell Thomas, N.B.C. in cock-pit of an A-26, 27-verso
    - 72. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Juvencourt Airfield, France. 11 Apr. 1945. Col. Robert Hughey, C.O. of Juvencourt Airfield left, talking to Lowell Thomas, N.B.C. in cock-pit of an A-26, 28
    - 73. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Florence, Italy 23-28 Apr. 1945. A Baily bridge constructed across the Arno River. The Germans blew up three out of the four bridges across the Arno River. They did not touch the famous Ponte Vecchio bridge because of its long historical background, 29
    - Verso: 73. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Florence, Italy 23-28 Apr. 1945. A Baily bridge constructed across the Arno River. The Germans blew up three out of the four bridges across the Arno River. They did not touch the famous Ponte Vecchio bridge because of its long historical background, 29-verso
    - 74. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Florence, Italy. 23-28 Apr. 1945. The Santa Croce church built in the year 1228. It is located in the heart of Florence, Italy, 30
    - Verso: 74. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Florence, Italy. 23-28 Apr. 1945. The Santa Croce church built in the year 1228. It is located in the heart of Florence, Italy, 30-verso
    - 77. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany 19 Apr. 1945. Gen. George S. Patton, Jr. talking to Dr. Bowles, Secretary of War's Stimson's special Asst. Photo made outside Gen. Patton's headquarters in Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany, 31
    - Verso: 77. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany 19 Apr. 1945. Gen. George S. Patton, Jr. talking to Dr. Bowles, Secretary of War's Stimson's special Asst. Photo made outside Gen. Patton's headquarters in Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany, 31-verso
    - 77. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany 19 Apr. 1945. Gen. George S. Patton, Jr. talking to Dr. Bowles, Secretary of War's Stimson's special Asst. Photo made outside Gen. Patton's headquarters in Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany, 32
    - Verso: 77. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany 19 Apr. 1945. Gen. George S. Patton, Jr. talking to Dr. Bowles, Secretary of War's Stimson's special Asst. Photo made outside Gen. Patton's headquarters in Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany, 32-verso
    - [General George S. Patton Jr. talking to Dr. Bowles], 33
    - 77. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany 19 Apr. 1945. Gen. George S. Patton, Jr. talking to Dr. Bowles, Secretary of War's Stimson's special Asst. Photo made outside Gen. Patton's headquarters in Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany, 34
    - Verso: 77. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany 19 Apr. 1945. Gen. George S. Patton, Jr. talking to Dr. Bowles, Secretary of War's Stimson's special Asst. Photo made outside Gen. Patton's headquarters in Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany, 34-verso
    - 77. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany 19 Apr. 1945. Gen. George S. Patton, Jr. talking to Dr. Bowles, Secretary of War's Stimson's special Asst. Photo made outside Gen. Patton's headquarters in Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany, 35
    - Verso: 77. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany 19 Apr. 1945. Gen. George S. Patton, Jr. talking to Dr. Bowles, Secretary of War's Stimson's special Asst. Photo made outside Gen. Patton's headquarters in Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany, 35-verso
  - Subject files: World War II (radio commentators tour of the war fronts), 1945; 2 (Box 1564)
    - 78. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany 10 Apr. 1945. Cesar Saerchinger, N.B.C. talking to two German civilians on entering ruined Cologne. In rear is Col. William Nuckols, PRO, 9th Air Force, E.T.O, 1
    - Verso: 78. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany 10 Apr. 1945. Cesar Saerchinger, N.B.C. talking to two German civilians on entering ruined Cologne. In rear is Col. William Nuckols, PRO, 9th Air Force, E.T.O, 1-verso
    - 79. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Near Eschwege, Germany 18 Apr. 1945. A team of oxen being driven by a Russian with his family riding in the farm wagon. These people are only some of the millions of displaced persons roaming the highways and byways of Germany now that they have been liberated by our Armed Forces, 2
    - Verso: 79. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Near Eschwege, Germany 18 Apr. 1945. A team of oxen being driven by a Russian with his family riding in the farm wagon. These people are only some of the millions of displaced persons roaming the highways and byways of Germany now that they have been liberated by our Armed Forces, 2-verso
    - 80. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Eschwege, Germany 18 Apr. 1945. Lt. Col. Richard S. Leghorn, of Winchester, Mass. C.O. of 67th Reconn. Group showing Howard Barnes, WOR, and Lowell Thomas NBC; the photos taken by his Reconn. Group of the Battle Fronts. On right back to camera is Capt. Harvey Monk, of Goldsboro, N. Carolina, 3
    - Verso: 80. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Eschwege, Germany 18 Apr. 1945. Lt. Col. Richard S. Leghorn, of Winchester, Mass. C.O. of 67th Reconn. Group showing Howard Barnes, WOR, and Lowell Thomas NBC; the photos taken by his Reconn. Group of the Battle Fronts. On right back to camera is Capt. Harvey Monk, of Goldsboro, N. Carolina, 3-verso
    - 81. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Reims, France. 16 Apr. 1945. Sgt. Leonard Dry, driver for General Dwight Eisenhower, in front of the Generals car, 4
    - Verso: 81. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Reims, France. 16 Apr. 1945. Sgt. Leonard Dry, driver for General Dwight Eisenhower, in front of the Generals car, 4-verso
    - 82. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Luxembourg City, Luxembourg, Germany 7 Apr. 45. Lowell Thomas, N.B.C. radio Commentator looking over war map in headquarters of 9th Air Force "War Room", 5
    - Verso: 82. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Luxembourg City, Luxembourg, Germany 7 Apr. 45. Lowell Thomas, N.B.C. radio Commentator looking over war map in headquarters of 9th Air Force "War Room", 5-verso
    - 83. Radio Commentator Tour Fronts. Germany?.Italy?10 Apr. 1945., Mr. Howard Barnes, of W.O.R. and the Herald Tribune, 6
    - Verso: 83. Radio Commentator Tour Fronts. Germany?.Italy?10 Apr. 1945., Mr. Howard Barnes, of W.O.R. and the Herald Tribune, 6-verso
    - 84. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Apr. 1945. Major Revais O'Neal, 9th Air Force Public Relations Officer who accompanied the Radio Commentators party over most of the European trip, 7
    - Verso: 84. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Apr. 1945. Major Revais O'Neal, 9th Air Force Public Relations Officer who accompanied the Radio Commentators party over most of the European trip, 7-verso
    - 85. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Germany?..Italy-10?.30 Apr. 1945. Johannes Steel, of W.H.N. Radio Commentator who toured the Fronts, 8
    - Verso: 85. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Germany?..Italy-10?.30 Apr. 1945. Johannes Steel, of W.H.N. Radio Commentator who toured the Fronts, 8-verso
    - 86. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. April 1945. Mr. Quincy Howe, C.B.S. Radio Commentator who toured the Fronts of Germany, 9
    - Verso: 86. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. April 1945. Mr. Quincy Howe, C.B.S. Radio Commentator who toured the Fronts of Germany, 9-verso
    - 87. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Apr. 1945. Lowell Thomas, N.B.C. Radio Commentator who toured the War Fronts, 10
    - Verso: 87. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Apr. 1945. Lowell Thomas, N.B.C. Radio Commentator who toured the War Fronts, 10-verso
    - 88. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Germany?? Italy. 10 Apr. 1945. Major William Hodapp [sic], Army Air Force, Bureau of Public Relations officer who conducted the group of radio commentators through Germany and Italy and return to New York, 11
    - Verso: 88. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Germany?? Italy. 10 Apr. 1945. Major William Hodapp [sic], Army Air Force, Bureau of Public Relations officer who conducted the group of radio commentators through Germany and Italy and return to New York, 11-verso
    - 88. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Germany?? Italy. 10 Apr. 1945. Major William Hodapp [sic], Army Air Force, Bureau of Public Relations officer who conducted the group of radio commentators through Germany and Italy and return to New York, 12
    - Verso: 88. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Germany?? Italy. 10 Apr. 1945. Major William Hodapp [sic], Army Air Force, Bureau of Public Relations officer who conducted the group of radio commentators through Germany and Italy and return to New York, 12-verso
    - 89. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. P.O.W. Camp near Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany. 18 Apr. 45. A truckload of prisoners waiting to unload at a P.O.W. camp near Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany, 13
    - Verso: 89. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. P.O.W. Camp near Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany. 18 Apr. 45. A truckload of prisoners waiting to unload at a P.O.W. camp near Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany, 13-verso
    - 90. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. P.O.W. Camp near Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany 18 Apr. 45. German Wacs resting on grass of their prisoner's cage after capture, 14
    - Verso: 90. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. P.O.W. Camp near Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany 18 Apr. 45. German Wacs resting on grass of their prisoner's cage after capture, 14-verso
    - 90. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. P.O.W. Camp near Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany 18 Apr. 45. German Wacs resting on grass of their prisoner's cage after capture, 15
    - Verso: 90. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. P.O.W. Camp near Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany 18 Apr. 45. German Wacs resting on grass of their prisoner's cage after capture, 15-verso
    - 91. Radio Commentators Tour of War Fronts. Reims, France. 16 Apr. 1945. Gen. Dwight Eisenhower, Supreme Commander of AEF, with the Group of Radio Commentators. Back to camera is Johannes Steel. In rear right is George Eamilton Combs, Center, talking to Gen. Eisenhower, is Mr. Thomas, 16
    - Verso: 91. Radio Commentators Tour of War Fronts. Reims, France. 16 Apr. 1945. Gen. Dwight Eisenhower, Supreme Commander of AEF, with the Group of Radio Commentators. Back to camera is Johannes Steel. In rear right is George Eamilton Combs, Center, talking to Gen. Eisenhower, is Mr. Thomas, 16-verso
    - [General Dwight D. Eisenhower, third from right, Lowell Thomas, right], 17
    - 92. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Enroute Paris over Germany 12 Apr. 1945. Cesar Saerchinger, N.B.C.; Howard Barnes W.O.R. and Herald Tribune and Lowell Thomas, N.B.C. They are looking over a map of Germany while enroute to Paris, France, 18
    - Verso: 92. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Enroute Paris over Germany 12 Apr. 1945. Cesar Saerchinger, N.B.C.; Howard Barnes W.O.R. and Herald Tribune and Lowell Thomas, N.B.C. They are looking over a map of Germany while enroute to Paris, France, 18-verso
  - Subject files: World War II (Lowell Thomas), circa 1943 - 1945; 3 (Box 1564)
    - LT with President Osmena, 1
    - Verso: LT with President Osmena, 1-verso
    - 30 April 1945; with the 15th Army Group in Italy; Lowell Thomas, radio commentator on a recent visit to General Mar. W. Clsrk, Commanding General, 15th Army Group; Photo by S/SGT S. Elson, 196th Signal Photo Co., CAU #1, 2
    - Verso: 30 April 1945; with the 15th Army Group in Italy; Lowell Thomas, radio commentator on a recent visit to General Mar. W. Clsrk, Commanding General, 15th Army Group; Photo by S/SGT S. Elson, 196th Signal Photo Co., CAU #1, 2-verso
    - 30 April 1945; with the 15th Army Group in Italy; Lowell Thomas, radio commentator on a recent visit to General Mar. W. Clsrk, Commanding General, 15th Army Group; Photo by S/SGT S. Elson, 196th Signal Photo Co., CAU #1, 3
    - Verso: 30 April 1945; with the 15th Army Group in Italy; Lowell Thomas, radio commentator on a recent visit to General Mar. W. Clsrk, Commanding General, 15th Army Group; Photo by S/SGT S. Elson, 196th Signal Photo Co., CAU #1, 3-verso
    - here's a picture - a rather good one - during World War two with Howard Barnes - we'd better put his name on the back - an air base in Europe; put with collection please; Verso: Howard Barnes, 4
    - Note: here's a picture - a rather good one - during World War two with Howard Barnes - we'd better put his name on the back - an air base in Europe; put with collection please; Verso: Howard Barnes, 5
    - With General Patton (at left) at advance headquarters Germany [Lowell Thomas at right], 6
    - Note: With General Patton (at left) at advance headquarters Germany [Lowell Thomas at right], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas, second from right, GENERAL George S. Patton, Jr., third from right], 8
    - [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, right, Lowell Thomas, left], 9
    - [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas, 10
    - General Cates, head of Marine Corps, with L.T. and the General's aide, 11
    - Verso: General Cates, head of Marine Corps, with L.T. and the General's aide, 11-verso
    - General Henry Arnold, Colonel Howard Rusk, L.T., etc., 12